So good round of applause.
Absolutely.
It feels so weird to not have questions,
but I said questions at the end, so we're
going to move on to our next performance.
Latent laughing Medusa.
Can you hear me?
Okay,
okay, I'm going to share it that way.
Having a body.
That is a sea.
I send you a message
from the underground.
My lips.
The T in torso.
I'm thinking from my mouth,
the mouth, the tongue, the tongue.
Can you hear my
tongue?
It's a letter.
Slither slippers away.
It's lister's.
Slithers, slithers
through and all
fist.
Sometimes we just let the show go on.
Sometimes we just say the line on time.
I'm glad there is a feature.
That can park my curtains and.
I'm in my inner.
A dancing.
And I'm staring through the opening.
Under
underground.
Am I staring through my mouth?
I think I'm staring through my lips.
Almost tearing through my eyes.
Almost said.
The lens.
I am spacious,
singing flesh on which is grafted.
No one knows which I more or less human,
but alive because of transformation.
Snake in the box one.
The snake in the box.
An age old parlor
trick designed to evoke surprise,
while one is exploring an as yet
unrecognized object.
The snake in the box problem
in graph theory and coding theory deals
with finding a certain
kind of path
along the edges of a hypercube.
This path starts at one corner and travels
along the edges to as many corners
as it can reach.
After it gets to a new corner,
the previous corner
and all of its neighbors
must be marked as unusable.
A snake in a box must never look back, nor
may it touch its own tube like body.
A soft coil awakes in my Morella.
The tide,
the sea.
Writing whether.
But let me start
with this example of the snake
in the box
phenomenon from my notebook yesterday.
I wrote this a few weeks ago, in the late
afternoon, I decided to look into buying
a new plant from my apartment
and some groceries for my sister's visit,
about two hours
before she would likely arrive in Chicago.
On the way to the garden shop,
I was interrupted by the appearance
of a fluffy white rug draped over a frame
outside of a shop in my neighborhood.
The rug reminded me exactly of a jacket
worn by my late maternal grandmother.
It also resembled a fluffy chair
in the audaciously
flamboyant vernacular of my grandmother's
living room in Queens.
I said to my sister inwardly,
that her visit had started early,
because we always reminisce about this
fabulous and infamous space
where I once walked by a series of narrow,
full length mirrors embedded in pink
wallpaper and silver winding pathways
under a gaudy crystalline chandelier.
Wearing oversize white heels and unaware
that my grandmother was watching
the image
of the fluffy rug, drew me into the store,
where I soon encountered a beautiful pink
colored jacket with a patchwork
of imagery
and colored panels lined at the bottom
in a trim of pink lace.
I stepped out of the bathroom.
It doubled as a dressing room
and said to the two workers at the shop
who happened to be standing nearby,
I'm surprised that this fits me so well.
I thought it would be
a small woman's jacket.
The young woman packed the jacket and rug
efficiently into a medium sized paper
bag, and it then looked like the carrier
for a small furry dog.
I continued with this small furry
dog onto the garden shop
and slipping
through the gate of an outdoor plaza,
I was interrupted
in the middle of my passage.
They had just closed.
It was already 4:00.
Once home,
I took the rug out and arranged it
carefully under the coffee table
where it seemed to belong.
I then opened a soft pack from the mail
and unwrapped for small wooden stakes,
snakes in boxes,
items of nostalgic trickery
that I had ordered from Etsy
for a performance I proposed in relation
to Helen Scissors The Laugh of the Medusa,
a text about women and writing itself
flowing from a female body,
shot through with streams of song
that was first published over 50 years
ago, in the year of my birth.
As I was putting groceries away
and straightening up my kitchen,
I heard a clank.
I looked down and saw a ring.
I checked my fingers and no ring
had fallen off, and looking more closely,
I saw that it was a ring
I had not seen before, with an iridescent
blue green gem
sitting atop an ornate Seville
silver base,
threading itself around the sides.
I put it on my left
finger and it fit perfectly.
When I awoke
in the bright light of the next morning,
I saw the ring on my side
table in detail for the first time.
The ornate designs were silver
coils of snakes.
The face was that of Medusa.
It is for this reason
that I am here with you today,
honoring my commitment
to perform a commitment
that was previous to this encounter
with the ring for many reasons.
Endangered.
Of course, I did a great deal of sleuthing
to decipher the meaning
of the rings appearance.
And here's the spoiler.
I returned to the store with my sister
and asked the young woman
if it looked like something
from their inventory.
She looked puzzled
and she said, that's my ring.
Helen Sassou flying is woman's gesture,
flying in language and making it fly.
I am heard
what my unavailable vertex
can taste the salt.
Helen Sassou.
Our mistakes are our leaps in the night.
Snake in the box two.
The headless of my desire,
that is my type
is stilled momentarily in a familiar form.
As the boy who only calls me daddy strings
the hard curve of his served
bow into the T in his torso,
sounds a call to an accumulated habit
of erotic expectation.
If I look at the coiling snakes of hair,
the real or fake
opals of eyes without the deployment
of a mirrored shield, I am stoned again
as the breeze is captured as a sign
that spells the breeze.
If my habits gravitate towards
coin shaped holes,
it is because the negative space of a
token has a depth made more capable
by carving disruption
into daytime patterns.
What good is a language
that can not be inverted?
A word that can't already have been hacked
in, hollowed out
to nest, and unexpected
creative cacophony.
Teasing the opening
with a G string of punctuation,
I am writing away from and towards, into,
and outside of the corporate capture
of human language.
Like a painter in the countryside
who is only vaguely aware
of a nearby war.
The unregulated sexual economy
of my neighborhood
thrives, like all capitalism
on scale, to the extent that to the extent
that the thrill of liberation is often
conflated with the desire for evidence
of measurable status,
at times this manifests
as a slanted line
that slashes through a set
of four recently
Sharpie bars, a grade school methodology
for counting transposed onto the hairy
skin of an ass
within which microscopic flagellates,
back tongues of ancestors, tail
flick, and countless jousts,
their feuding forces soaked cathartic
into the eager
lining of a generously rewarded host.
Helen Susu.
Let's hurry.
The continent is not impenetrable.
Dark. I've been there often.
I was overjoyed one day to run in to
Jean Genet.
Making the box
keyhole.
After the injection
of the first treatment,
I recall stretching my arm out into space
like an infant
who grasps at something invisible
that they might one day grow into.
I wondered if this motion corresponded
to the new birth of neurons by injection.
Seven
my body moved involuntarily in simple
but repetitive, unexpected choreographies,
as automatic speech gave way to song
and then to moaning,
and the energetic abyss
moved through me into my navel
and out through my perennial.
Why do the tech oligarchs
swear by ketamine?
What is the connection
between llms and dissociation?
This phenomenon of disconnection
as the deepest form of intimacy,
of being dis m embodied.
Large language models
are generally built to compress
probability mass, to move towards
regions of latent space where
many plausible continuations overlap.
The latent laughing
medusa produces a different operation
to proliferate as an embodied flow
that edges
without touching itself.
In the box.
The latent laughing Medusa.
It's been shown
that laughter can reconnect us
to the pleasure of our bodies,
and that the body does not know
the difference between real and fake.
Laughter. Laughs.
Speak any hard
when you've had enough of the phantasm,
let it go entirely and continue
only with ha ha ha.
At this point
you will transcend language and your lips
will fall out of sync
with the words that you are speaking.
You will reach maximum higher laughter
altitude.
Please feel free to join me
in these last words and let them go.
When you feel ready.
Or please feel free
to try this later on at home.
The first word is hand Ta'zim.
That's phantasm without a P.
And in
Assam. And.
The second word is
the second token two word phrase
handed down.
Handed down.
Down.
The third phrase is hard on.
Hard on.
Hard on
tender.
Coil remembers the emerging
serpentine language.
Tender coils of language
unbutton the tide of my belt.
Ha ha!
Harbors.
Ha ha
ha ha!
Ha ha!
Harbors.
Ha ha ha!
Vowels.
Open under latent vowels
without touching its own alphabet.
Having a body.
Having a body
that through with streams of song.
Having a body.
That is at sea.
Sooner stop the sea.
The Len susu.
There's her sea.
But look.
Our seas are what we make of them.
Full of fish or not.
Opaque or transparent.
Red or black.
High or smooth, narrow or bank less.
And we are ourselves.
Sea. Sand. Coral.
Seaweed. Beaches.
Tide. Swimmers. Children's waves.
More or less. Waverly.
Sea. Earth. Sky.
What matter would rebuff us
when we know how to speak them all?
Sooner stop the sea.
You can say it once or twice
along with me.
Or say it later at home.
Sooner stop the sea.
Sooner stop the sea,
the sea.
Oh nacre of parle.
Oh, naked pearl Meridian.
Milk of mare at sea.
Bush boy.
Hush!